hurlmedia.design 2018-08-21

# Privacy – HurlMedia

###### Privacy Policy for Hurlmedia Applications

At Hurlmedia, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.

This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Hurlmedia and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at support@hurlmedia.com

###### Cookies and Web Beacons

Like any other website or mobile application, Hurlmedia uses ‘cookies’.

These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited.

The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page or mobile app content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.

###### Our Advertising Partners

Some of advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.

  * Google Admobhttps://www.google.com/admob

###### Privacy Policies

You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Hurlmedia.

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Hurlmedia or our mobile applications.

They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs.

These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that Hurlmedia has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

###### Third Pary Privacy Policies

Hurlmedia’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites.

Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information.

It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.

###### Children’s Information

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet.

We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

Hurlmedia does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13.

If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

###### Consent

By using our mobile applications, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
